[
    {
        "title" : "Opening Song Lyrics"
    },


    {
      "id": 1,
      "question": "How many special people change? How many lives are livin' strange?",
      "answer": "Oasis - Champagne Supernova"
    },
    {
        "id": 2,
        "question": "I thought I saw a man brought to life, He was warm, he came around like he was dignified",
        "answer": "Natalie Imbruglia - Torn"
    },
    {
        "id": 3,
        "question": "We're talking away, I don't know what I'm to say",
        "answer": "Aha - Take On Me"
      },
      {
          "id": 4,
          "question": "Sometimes I feel I've got to run away, I've got to get away",
          "answer": "Soft Cell - Tainted Love"
      },
      {
        "id": 5,
        "question": "We're no strangers to love, You know the rules and so do I ",
        "answer": "Rick Astley - Never Gonna Give You Up"
      },
      {
          "id": 6,
          "question": "It's not time to make a change, Just relax, take it easy",
          "answer": "Cat Stevens - Father And Son"
      },
      {
        "id": 7,
        "question": "I've never seen a diamond in the flesh, I cut my teeth on wedding rings in the movies",
        "answer": "Lorde - Royals"
      },
      {
          "id": 8,
          "question": "She take my money when I'm in need, Yeah, she's a triflin' friend indeed",
          "answer": "Kanye West - Golddigger"
      },
      {
        "id": 9,
        "question": "We're caught in a trap, I can't walk out",
        "answer": "Elvis Presley - Suspicious Minds"
      },
      {
          "id": 10,
          "question": "You were working as a waitress in a cocktail bar, When I met you",
          "answer": "The Human League - Don't You Want Me"
      }
]
  